If we bring the left foot here to meet it and bend the knees and then bring the chest back forward you get a nice line in the body.
Now it's very important to try this in front of a mirror so you can make sure your shoulders stay forward.
It's very easy to start doing this.
This is not the move, this could be a variation of the move but it's not the move.
We're just twisting the lower body slightly to present our audience with our working hip step.
Hip.
Step.
Let's try it together.
Hip.
So shoulders stay square walking forward and step.
Feet come together knees line up same direction.
Step.
You don't want your knees going out here right?
Knees together lift.
Step.
Lift.
Forward step.
Step.
Lift.
Slight angle very good.
Try it in the mirror it looks more complicated.
It looks very easy but it's actually it takes a lot of concentration to keep those shoulders forward.